Guide to the Stanford Humanities Center, Harry Camp Memorial Lectures, Videorecordings
Stanford University Libraries
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford Humanities Center, Harry Camp Memorial lectures, videorecordings
2002-2006
V0253
Stanford Humanities Center.
0.5 linear foot
Collection includes VHS tapes of Anthony Sampson's lecture "Mandela, Reconciliation and Shakespeare," 2002; VHS tapes and DVDcam tape of Elaine Pagel's lectures on the Gospel of Thomas and politics and religion, 2004; and DVDcam and DVD discs of Anthony Grafton's lectures "The First Theorists of History" and "The Life and Death of a Genre," 2006.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Stanford University Libraries 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: speccollref@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://www-sul.stanford.edu/depts/spc/spc.html
Administrative Information
Information about Access
Videotapes that are not VHS will need to be reformatted prior to use.
Biographical/Historical Sketch
The Harry Camp Memorial Fund was established in 1956 by friends and associates of Harry Camp. A prominent businessman and philanthropist in San Francisco, Camp was described as "a gentle and wise humanitarian." The fund brings outstanding speakers to the University for public lectures and promotes the study of "the concept of the dignity and the worth of the individual."
Description of the Collection
Collection includes VHS tapes of Anthony Sampson's lecture "Mandela, Reconciliation and Shakespeare," 2002; VHS tapes and DVDcam tape of Elaine Pagel's lectures on the Gospel of Thomas and politics and religion, 2004; and DVDcam and DVD discs of Anthony Grafton's lectures "The First Theorists of History" and "The Life and Death of a Genre," 2006.
Access Terms
Grafton, Anthony.; Pagels, Elaine H., 1943-; Sampson, Anthony.; Stanford Humanities Center.
Collection Contents
- Videorecordings
  - Stanford Humanities: Anthony Sampson (Window Dub) (copy 1 of 2), January 22, 2002; 1 videotape (VHS); V253.1 (Box 1)
  - Stanford Humanities: Anthony Sampson (Window Dub) (copy 2 of 2), January 22, 2002; 1 videotape (VHS); V253.2 (Box 1)
  - Stanford University Humanities Center Presents Elaine Pagels, Religious Historian, Princeton University, Cubberley Auditorium (copy 1 of 2), January 26, 2004; 1 videotape (VHS); V253.3 (Box 1)
  - Stanford University Humanities Center Presents Elaine Pagels, Religious Historian, Princeton University, Cubberley Auditorium (copy 2 of 2), January 26, 2004; 1 videotape (VHS); V253.4 (Box 1)
  - Stanford University Humanities Center Presents Elaine Pagels, Religious Historian, Princeton University, Stanford Law School (copy 1 of 4), January 28, 2004; 1 videotape (VHS); V253.5 (Box 1)
  - Stanford University Humanities Center Presents Elaine Pagels, Religious Historian, Princeton University, Stanford Law School. (copy 2 of 4), January 28, 2004; 1 videotape (VHS); V253.6 (Box 1)
  - Stanford University Humanities Center Presents Elaine Pagels, Religious Historian, Princeton University, Stanford Law School. (copy 3 of 4), January 28, 2004; 1 videotape (VHS); V253.7 (Box 1)
  - Stanford University Humanities Center Presents Elaine Pagels, Religious Historian, Princeton University, Stanford Law School (copy 4 of 4), January 28, 2004; 1 videotape (VHS); V253.13 (Box 1)
  - Elaine Pagels, January 28, 2004; videotape (DVCAM); V253.8 (Box 1)
  - Stanford Humanities Center Harry Camp Memorial Lecture: Anthony Grafton: The First Theorists of History, January 30, 2006; optical disc (DVD); V253.9 (Box 1)
  - H. Camp Memorial Lecture, GRAFTON, January 30, 2006; videotape (DVCAM); V253.10 (Box 1)
  - Stanford Humanities Center Harry Camp Memorial Lecture: Anthony Grafton: The Life and Death of a Genre, February 1, 2006; optical disc (DVD); V253.11 (Box 1)
  - H. Camp Memorial Lecture, GRAFTON, February 1, 2006; videotape (DVCAM); V253.12 (Box 1)